Narrator: 1A
M: Hello.
Hi.
What’s your name?
Nice to meet you.
A cappuccino, please.
A tea.
Yes.
No.
OK.
Thanks.
Sorry.
Just a minute.
Goodbye. / Bye.
See you on Friday.
See you tomorrow.
Narrator: 1B
F: Where are you from?
I’m from Spain.
Where’s Genoa?
I think it’s in Italy.
It’s a nice city.
I don’t know.
Very good.
Wow!
Narrator: 2A
M: Excuse me.
Are they free?
Are you on holiday?
We’re on business.
What’s that?
Have a nice day!
It’s a beautiful city.
tourists
dogs
over there
Narrator: 2B
M: Who's he?
How old is he?
He's very good-looking.
How are you?
I’m fine.
This is Alex.
That’s my bus.
This is my bus stop.
What class are you in?
What’s your phone number?
See you later.
a bedroom
a kitchen
a garden
big
small
in the south of England